AGNES GELLER FRONT- END WEB DEVELOPER, INTERNATIONAL FREIGHT FORWARDER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Front-End Web Developer with a solid foundation in Logistics and Supply Chain Management, complemented by a certificate from the EDx Bootcamp. Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, and Node, with a focus on APIs and user experience design. Demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively in team settings and navigate high-pressure situations. Committed to creating web applications that enhance user efficiency and ease.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Technical Languages: HTML, JavaScript, CSS, UX, Git, GitHub, Information architecture, User experience design, Modern front-end frameworks, Structuring, positioning, and optimisation of web page content, React.js, Netlify Developing with APIs, JavaScript framework, DOM manipulation, Web-based applications, Data extraction and retrieval, Git, GitHub, jQuery, RESTful compliant Network.

EDUCATION

EDx Bootcamp Front - End Web Developer Certificate

FRONT- END WEB DEVELOPER | NOV 2023 - MARCH 2024

HTML , CSS, avaScript framework, UX/UI desing, Information architecture, user experience design, modern front-end frameworks. Structuring, positioning, and optimisation of web page content. React.js, Developing with APIs, Bootstrap, DOM manipulation. Webbased applications, Data extraction and retrieval, Git, GitHub, jQuery, RESTful compliant Network, Slack, Netlify

Level 2 Principle of Coding Level 2 Principle of Cyber Security

CENTRE OF EXCELLENT | JUNE 2022 - JUNE 2023

MLE Magyar Logisztikai Egyesulet

Logistics Administrator International Road Freight Forwarding

WORK HISTORY

Cleaning Service Management CLEANING SIMPLE | MAY 2014 - PRESENT

Oversaw operations at a cleaning company, providing quotes, assessing homes, and calculating service prices. Managed logistics by transporting cleaners, and ensuring the provision of necessary cleaning supplies.

EasyJet Check in Agent, Passenger Service Officer LONDON GATWICK AIRPORT | JUNE 2022 - OCT 2023

Validating customer's documentation for travel. Processing customers for boarding. Processing customers using manual and automated systems. Assisting customers during disruption. Ensuring compliance in both airline and airport policies.

Amazon and Yodel Delivery Organizer WEST SUSSEX | MAY 2014 - JAN 2022

Facilitated efficient delivery operations at Amazon and Yodel, coordinating route planning and package distribution. Ensured timely and accurate deliveries by monitoring logistics and addressing any delivery-related challenges.

Internation Freight Forwarder G & G HIGH QUALITY KFT. BUDAPEST, HUNGARY | JUNE 2005 - OCT 2011

Ibusz Logistics Freight Forwarding Shipping Team Leader 2008 - 2011

As the owner of a thriving business, I spearheaded comprehensive shipping operations, staff management, and administrative tasks including TimoCom utilization and invoice generation. My role extended to strategic marketing, negotiations, and fostering partnerships with key stakeholders. Responsible for teaching Freight Forwarder System for team members.

CONTACT DETAILS

Mobile: +447546371504 Email: darlingagnes@gmail.com Portfolio: https://agika.netlify.app GitHub: https://github.com/AgnesGeller